Guide to the Sao Tome And Principe Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sao Tome and Principe collection
1980-2012
MS 1538
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.77
(4 boxes)
The collection consists of printed material relating to political and economic conditions in Sao Tome and Principe.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the African Collection Curator.
Associated Materials
African Collection, MS 605; Pamphlet Collection, MS 1351; African Postcard Collection, MS 1575. Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The material in the original accession is arranged chronologically. Additions to the collection may vary in arrangement.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of printed material relating to political and economic conditions in Sao Tome and Principe.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Sao Tome and Principe -- Economic conditions; Sao Tome and Principe -- Politics and government; Movimento de Libertação de S. Tomé e Príncipe
- Inventory, 1980-1988
  - Regulamento Interno dos Grupos do Controlo Popular, Assembleia Popular Nacional, 1980 November (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Libertação de São Tomé e Príncipe (MLSTP): journals, papers, speeches, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Democratização da vida politica e económica de São Tomé e Príncipe: Conferência de imprensa com o Presidente Pinto da Costa, 1987 November (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Discurso Proferido..., Aquando da Passagem do XIII. Aniversário da Proclamação da Independência Nacional, Assembleia Popular Nacional, 1988 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, 1986-1994; Accession 1995-M-198
  - Additional printed materials, 1986-1994, undated (Box 1)
- Additional Material, 1988-1989; Accession 2010-M-115
  - Caderno Revolução, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Revolução Semanário (5 copies), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional material, 2010, 2012; Accession 2015-M-001
  - Printed material, 2010, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)